Contact

loriallmon28@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lori-allmon-b8205785 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Hospitals Healthcare

Lori Allmon

Corporate Interim CNO

Columbus, Ohio Area

Summary

Experienced Chief Nursing Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Acute Care, Critical Care, Hospitals, Healthcare Management, and Healthcare. Strong business development professional with a MSN focused in Master of Science in Nursing from University of Phoenix.

Experience

Select Specialty Hospital

12 years

Corporate Interim CNO

November 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Market Chief Nursing Officer

January 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 11 months)

Columbus, Ohio Area

Chief Nursing Officer

2008 - January 2017 (9 years)

Columbus, Ohio

Education

University of Phoenix

MSN, Master of Science in Nursing